Hello.
I'm Mayu Tamura from Nagasaka 46.
I'm Kaoru Katsurahara.
I'm Satsuki Sugawara.
This is Aya Ogawa.
We're here in Shimane Prefecture.
Here we are.
As far as the eye can see, there's a lot of nature.
Yes, it is.
The air is really nice and it's already fun.
Actually, we are in a place called Okuizumo-cho in Shimane Prefecture.
Population is about 11,000
Area is about 368 square kilometers.
I don't know.
If my calculations are correct, it's the equivalent of 7,830 Tokyo Domes.
That's great.
At any rate, it's amazing.
It's just that it feels like a lot of space.
I see.
Why are we here in Okuizumo Town?
To commemorate the one million subscribers to our channel.
We are here in Okuizumo Town to carry out a project to make dreams come true for Nogizaka46.
We came here to Okuizumo Town.
Here we are!
By the way, we received about 12,000 applications!
That's amazing!
We were chosen out of 12,000 to participate in the project!
To Shimane Prefecture!
I'm so glad we came!
That's great!
Please read Aya's letter to see what kind of applications we received!
Please read Aya's letter!
The letter is from
Mr. Kuwatani, 54 years old
I work at a high school in Okuizumo Town, Shimane Prefecture.
Every year around the end of May, we plant brand rice
We plant rice with high school students and local elementary school students around the end of May.
I would be very happy if I could plant rice together with the members!
We would also like everyone to enjoy the harvested rice!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you got the message that I don't think you read it well enough.
Have you guys ever done rice planting?
Yes, I have.
Me too.
Am I the only one?
It's my first rice planting.
My first rice planting.
Best memory.
I want to have a lot of experiences, but I also want to go to Yokota High School where Mr. Kuwatani works to make her dream come true.
In order to make your dream come true, I'd like to go to Yokota High School where you work.
Shall we go right away?
Shall we go?
Let's go!
Let's go to Yokota High School, the only high school in Kuniizumo Town where Mr. Kuwatani works!
I wonder if she's some kind of a changeling...
Let's go!
Wow!
What club were you in?
That's the last thing you want to hear from me.
North Division.
I'm not in it now, but I was in the brass band department in middle school.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You're so cute.
Clarinet
So cute.
So here we are.
Look, is he over there?
Oh!
Kuwatani?
Yes, Kuwatani.
Hello.
This is Mr. Takeshi Kuwatani who applied for this contest.
How did you get hooked on Nogizaka?
I started watching youtube videos of the Nogizaka Under Construction that was going on.
I thought that the students nowadays are not only studying but also trying to learn how to live in the society.
They are trying to learn how to live in the society besides studying.
In the midst of this, there are many things that students can't acquire in the classroom.
For example, the ability to develop one's talents or to turn one's weaknesses into strengths.
I saw that kind of thing on the show and thought it would be very helpful for me.
That's how I became a fan.
Thank you very much.
Actually, Taue will be over by the middle of May.
But this time, Nogizaka members are coming to the show.
Mr. Kuwatani cooperated with us to hold the rice planting event on short notice.
We were completely unaware that you all would be coming today.
So we're preparing a surprise for them.
I've come to think of it not just a rice planting, so I'm
I'm so excited!
There's even a stroke mark on it.
I've tried to give them a hint, but I don't think they'll notice.
Of course, they don't know that we're coming.
We currently have about 10 members, including children.
I'd like to add more people to the group.
I'd like to increase the number of participants.I'd like to add a few more people since we're here.
Do you know where I can find students?
Actually, the amount of students who are enrolling from out of state is right there.
I'm heading that way, and I'm sure there are a few of them.
I'd like to talk to the students a little bit.
Yay!
So we're going to start looking for people who are willing to rice planting with us.
How many people live in the dormitory?
There are about 30 students living here.
Some of them are participating in club activities and tournaments.
So we don't have all of them.
So there are three of us.
I think some of them are in the school.
I haven't said that word in a while.
Pounding.
That's right, this is the quantity.
The one on the left is the old building, but it's for the boys.
The newer one on the right is for the girls.
I'm excited to see the quantities.
The atmosphere is very exciting.
I don't know how many people are in the room, but I'm going to call them.
I wonder if they'll reach it.
But we're idols, so... we usually stir things up.
That's true.
Kakki and the other guys are really aggressive.
No, he's miked.
Why are you losing your voice?
Why are you yelling?
I'll say, "Anybody home?
I'll say "Anybody home?" and then I'll go on with my appeal.
"Nogizaka46!
Let's say "Nogizaka46".
Let's say it!
Nogizaka46!
Wow!
It's like we're calling them "Nogizaka46" now.
It's so cool!
Shall we tell them about the rice planting?
That's true.
That's a good idea.
Let's do it!
Let's plant rice together!
That's great.
That's amazing.
It's gonna bring out the best in me.
I did it!
Hello.
Hello, there.
Come here, everyone.
Come on in.
She just wanted to show her face for a second.
I don't know.
Oh, here she is.
What do you think?
There's a lot of girls here.
Oh, hello, there they are.
Wow, a lot of girls.
Oh, my God.
Do you want to come downstairs?
Oh, you want to go downstairs?
Can I go down there?
Can I go downstairs?
Yes!
So cute. So cute.
Let's go downstairs.
So we're off to the dorm to meet the Pure Girls.
Will they be there for rice planting?
Oh, they're coming to pick us up.
They're coming to get us!
There's so many of them
Hello.
That's a hell of a chess game.
Hello. - Hello.
I'm so happy to see you. Were you all at the dormitory today?
Yes, we were. We were playing club.
What club? The rice bowl club.
I saw you at the club earlier.
I'm a big fan of aikal zurulu.
He's so cute!
He's cute.
I'm so happy.
I'll go a little closer.
Do you want to go a little closer?
How long have you been here?
Actually, I came here today to do a town meeting.
We're going to have a town meeting at 2:00 p.m.
I'm going to have a town meeting at 2:00 p.m., and I wanted to ask if you guys would like to come.
Will you come?
Thank you.
After getting their rice-planting friends safely
We parted from the students at this point.
to the Yokota Community Center, where announcements could be made
Yokota Community Center
Good afternoon.
This is Mr. Abe, the community center director.This is Mr. Abe, the community center director.
This is Mr. Abe, the director of the Yokota Community Center, and I look forward to working with you.
Pleased to meet you.
This time, we'd like to gather people to play the town.
We'd like to do a broadcast.
That's all right.
Thank you very much.
That's great. That's great.
I thought you said no. You're right.
This broadcast is only for homes in the Yokota district.
As soon as you put down the receiver, the broadcast will begin.
Hello, Yokota residents!
I'm Abe, the director of the Yokota Community Center.
I'd like to inform you of an event that will be held in Yokota this afternoon.
I'd like to make this announcement not to me.
I would like to ask this gentleman to make the announcement.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Hello to everyone living in the Yokota area of Oku-Aikama Town.
We are Mayu Tamura, a member of an idol group called Nogizaka46.
I am Kakihara.
I am Satsuki Sugawara.
I am Aya Ogawa.
Excuse me for this sudden announcement on a day off.
Actually, we came to Okuizumo Town today to plant rice in the rice field behind Izumo Yokota Station at 2:00 p.m. with local residents.
Whether you know us or not, let's plant rice together.
If you would like to help us plant rice, we would appreciate it if you would wear clothes that are suitable for rice planting.
This is the announcement from Nogizaka46.
The next session ended amidst a tense atmosphere.
I'm sure I did it. I'm sure I did.
It must have been too tight.
What, the flow?
What, from there?
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming!
Here it comes!
I would like to inform you about an event that will be held in the Yokota area from Lo.
I would like to ask you, not me, to be our guest.
Hello to everyone living in the Yokota area of Okuizumo Town.
We are members of an idol group called Nogizaka46 and we are Mai Tamura.
I am Haruka Kaki.
I am Satsuki Sugawara.
I am Aya Ogawa.
About 2,400 people live here.
We're going to make a simultaneous announcement to the Towata area, which is home to about 2,400 people.
I wonder how many people will come.
It looks like we have 30 minutes until 2:00 p.m.
Let's wait!
And the appointed time
Ta-da!
I've changed my clothes!
I've changed my clothes to the fashion for rice planting
I've changed my clothes.
Stylish!
Everyone is wearing
Ribbons
I put on the ribbon on my right breast
On the right breast
I guess it's a shame if idols don't wear ribbons.
So, since it's already 2:00 p.m.
I'd like to go to the rice planting site.
Let's go.
I've done a lot of advertising.
Yes, we did.
I was wondering if you'd be there.
I don't know if he's here.
You know, earlier...
Just the girls who were so happy to see me.
There are so many of them.
I wonder if they're enjoying it.
There's a lot of them.
So many... hello.
Hello. - Hello.
Did you all hear the announcement?
Yes, I did.
Thank you very much.
They heard the announcement and came to the rice paddies.
And they came to the rice paddies.
About 50 people
from Okuidumo town.
Why don't you listen to the announcement?
They heard the announcement.
Don't be nervous.
I'll do my best.
Here's a little com show.
Well...
Thank you all for coming.
Thank you very much.
Did you hear the announcement earlier?
Yes.
Here they are.
Thank you very much.
Let's do countryside together from here.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
This time, we will plant a variety of rice called Mitamai.
It is said to be the Onuma of the East and the Futata of the West, and is a representative brand of rice of Okuizumi Town.
The rice field we will plant this time is 600 square meters in size!
After listening carefully to how rice planting is done, the work finally begins!
I want the students to know the joy of rice planting.I want my students to know the joy of rice planting.
Mr. Kuwatani's dream is finally coming true!
May I ask everyone to come in?
Off you go, everyone!
I wonder where we're starting from?
Certainly.
Please.
Wow!
Oh, no, no, no!
Well then, I look forward to working with you.
Here we go!
Now it's time to go to the town!
How big is 30 centimeters?
That's right.
How much is 30 centimeters?
I'm too stupid to know.
Wait, this is short.
I feel like I'm taking too much!
Am I okay?
I thought you said two or three minutes.
No, you got it, Aya.
Are you guys having fun at school?
I'm having fun.
You're having fun?
Yes, I am.
What do you enjoy most about school?
Recess.
I know what you mean.
Sorry, that's funny.
I used to love recess too.
Wait a minute. Frog, Frog, Frog.
Frog, frog, frog, frog.
Frog, frog, frog.
How did you do that?
How did you do that? You're gonna step on it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What are you guys doing?
Spread your legs apart.
Spread your legs apart?
What's your name?
Halki, you wrote it for me.
It's just like you taught me.
How old are you now?
I'm in my third year of high school.
The same age?
The same age.
How old are you?
Seventeen.
So you're high school seniors.
A junior or senior?
I'm a freshman.
What do you do on your days off?
Just hanging out.
If it's not just hanging around...
What do you do for fun?
He wants to drink.
That's great. Thank you.
Have you ever been to a live concert?
I have.
I see. I see.
I'd love to.
I'd love for you to come. I'll spread my legs.
It's been eight years.
That's amazing.
That's longer than I've been here.
Look at the side.
They're not fast.
They're unbelievably fast, but they're all...
But they're all struggling to get out.
Go on.
You're fast.
I'm getting called out on my own.
You're early.
Do you know Nogizaka?
I'm glad.
By the way, my name is...
Ogawa Aika.
I'm so glad.
By the way, you know my name.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for calling you that.
Shokichi.
That's right.
I'm Shokichi.
I'm so embarrassed.
What am I going to do?
It's spread all the way to Shimane.
What to do?
We've been planting rice for 15 minutes.
Look at our feet!
They're coming.
What?
What do you mean, "It's coming"?
A trolley train is going to pass through Okuidumo Town.
Yes...
Wait a minute!
Wait for the train!Wait for the Essiel train.
Wait.
Wow.
Wow, Mr. Essiel.
Oh, there you are.
Wow.
There's so many on board.
You've got a lot on your plate!
Finally, the persimmon's legs came loose...
Let's go!
Here we go.
Yes, OK!
In spite of the slanting angle, he is already dashing!
I'm sure.
The sound is
Amazing!
Actually, this Okuizumo Uzengo
will be out of service this November.
Bye bye!
Okun, Okun, Okun...
Bye-bye!
Bye bye bye
Yay!
Amazing.
They seem to be very satisfied with this precious experience.
This is something, isn't it?
I want to come back when the rice is grown properly.
Please come!
I want to go all the way to the rice harvest.
When the rice dies...
I want to come back.
Wow, that's great.
Oh, he's here, too.
Yes, I want some.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, can I have it?
I'm on the softball team.
Oh, from the back.
A little, uh, in return.
Oh, anywhere at all.
Oh, close, close.
Nice try.
sludgy
Oh, here
Wow!
so close!
I enjoyed it.
Hey, it's fun, isn't it?
The time is 15:00
We decided to take a break here
I'm chafing
Gentlemen.
Yes, ma'am.
As you can see...
I'm so glad you could join us.
What a surprise... He said he heard the announcement in town earlier.
A bento shop owner
He brought us onigiri (rice balls)!
Thank you very much!
Everyone was so happy, weren't they?
They were so happy!
Thank you very much.
Everyone!
Because you can't plant rice if you're hungry
So we all decided to take a break for rice balls!
Okay, here we go!
Bon appétit!
Wow!
How is it?
It's good.
Bon appétit!
The rice is delicious
It stings
I'm so happy
I asked Yu-chan about this earlier
Are you guys having fun at school?
Yes, we are.
I'm happy.
What do you enjoy the most?
What are you doing?
I'm having fun in my club.
Youth.
Ball team is cool.
It suits you.
Really?
It's an experience.
Well, next time you come to the island...
I'll try ballroom dancing.
I'll be a new member.
Come on in.
He said it's okay.
I did it.
He's gonna teach me.
I'm glad.
On the other hand, I'm...
I'm nervous.
Do you guys have any dreams for the future?Do you have any dreams for the future?
Yeah, I dream about it.
Dreams for the future?
A stylist.
Maybe...
Maybe we'll work together in the future.
Oh, my God.
She's cute.
So, maybe after high school, you'll go to a vocational school?
Yes, ma'am.
Maybe we'll work together in the future.
Ah...
They planted rice together.
We planted rice together.
Remember?
Maybe we'll work together in the future.
I have to work hard too.
You're a great inspiration.
I'm glad.
I don't usually get a chance to talk to students.
In the midst of the first
It's time to start planting rice again!
Let it be delicious!
Let's make it delicious!
Yes, I'm going to get carried away
Ready, go!
I'm having so much fun!
Loud enough to be heard
With a big voice
Loud and a little bit tasty
Let's go!
Be delicious!
You'll be saved.
It'll help.
Taste good!
I hope it tastes good.
Say it in a cute voice.
Yes, Mai Tamura.
You don't sound like her.
I told you to practice.
Who can imitate my voice?
If you say there's someone who can do it...
Isn't it amazing?
Mai Tamura.
She did it.
Can you do it, Satchan? Please be serious. I'm Mai Tamura.
It's not moving at all.
This is serious. It's Mai Tamura.
Not bad...
Shirakai.
Dirty.
I wonder if it's like that.
Hey, sorry, something like that.
I hope they grow up okay.
I feel like I could stay here forever.
I'm getting a little attached to it.
I know, it's fun.
I want to watch over the seedlings until they...
I want to watch over it until it grows up.
That's for sure.
I'll be back...
Around the time I planted it.
I'd like to come back when it's ready.
You know, I really do.
We've been at it for about two hours now.
Only one plot left to plant!
To make Mr. Kuwata's dream come true
In the midst of unfamiliar work
The members earnestly planting seedlings while having fun at the same time.
And above all, the students of Yokota High School
And the combined efforts of the people of Okuizumo Town.
Finally
Let's do it!
Let's make it tasty!
Good!
It's good.
That's it.
It's done.
Now it tastes good.
See, we can have some fun now.
I can do it.
Okay, everybody, we're done.
We're done.
Thank you very much.
So, rice planting is over!
It's done!
That's great.
Look, it's all done!
It's really done!
That's great!
How was everyone?
It was my first time planting rice.
It was a lot of fun.
I got mud on my face in the process.
But even that was a lot of fun.
It was a great experience.It was a great experience!
It was nice to know that you know us as far as Shimane.
It was also fun to talk a lot with them.
It was our first time to broadcast in the town.
I see.
I was a little nervous.
You did a great job. All of it.
Really?
You were good.
Osawa, you were good.
And Kakki?
I had fun, too.
We were out in nature.
We all had fun talking and planting rice together.
I haven't done that in a long time.
It was really relaxing.
And I got to hear about their dreams for the future.
It was really nice.
All the kids are looking toward the future.
I thought it was so wonderful.
I thought that we can do our best in the future, too.
I hadn't planted rice since I was in elementary school.
I felt like I was in my youth.
The students were so energetic.
Everyone had their own dreams.
I learned a lot about their daily lives.
Above all, the onigiri were delicious!
They were delicious.
I knew they were delicious.
I'm looking forward to seeing the seedlings we planted grow right away!
Obviously, it's Forty Cheeks!
My favorite snack!
It was so much fun!
Did you make your dreams come true?
I made my dream come true by having you guys plant rice with the high school students... and I also made my dream come true by having you guys work so hard!
And after all the hard work you've put in...
I'd like to make sure it gets to you.
Really?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it!
It's true!
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it
Seino
Famous completion